<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Benedict Pak</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/</link><description>Recent content on Benedict Pak</description><image><url>https://benedictpak.com/logo.png</url><link>https://benedictpak.com/logo.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 23:20:10 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://benedictpak.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MoneyGoWhere</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/projects/moneygowhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 23:20:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/projects/moneygowhere/</guid><description>A personal finance budgeting app for tech-savvy students. If you dislike using the mouse, this application is made for you!
MoneyGoWhere is a personal finance application targeted at students at the National University of Singapore (NUS). It allows students to keep track of all their spending and their related information such as date, cost and tags. Users can also set budget goals, view statistics, set reminders for bills, view exchange rates, use different currencies, and import and export their data.</description></item><item><title>Doke Chatbot</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/projects/doke-chatbot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 23:10:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/projects/doke-chatbot/</guid><description>Doke is a chatbot designed to help you manage tasks, while being fun and interactive. Independently built as a Software Engineering project.
To learn more, click here.</description></item><item><title>When Can Meet?</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/projects/when-can-meet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 23:00:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/projects/when-can-meet/</guid><description>A single page web-app for hassle-free meetings and a RESTful API containing CRUD functionality.
To view the code, click here.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio Site V1</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/projects/portfolio-site/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:47:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/projects/portfolio-site/</guid><description>Built to practice creating and designing a website from scratch using the popular Bootstrap 4 framework.
This is an older version of the portfolio site.</description></item><item><title>Trashy Floor</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/projects/trashy-floor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 22:46:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/projects/trashy-floor/</guid><description>Endless runner mobile game, endless fun!
Available on Google Play.</description></item><item><title>Starting up a blog</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/blog/starting-up-a-blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 20:51:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/blog/starting-up-a-blog/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally re-written my site and this is version 2!
As part of the upgrade, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share more about static site generators. I used Hugo and PaperMod to build this site, along with GitHub Pages as part of the workflow.
Why perform a rewrite? I had 2 new use-cases:
Add new content Avoid duplicating code Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at both versions 1 and 2 of the website to see how the use-cases are met.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://benedictpak.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benedictpak.com/about/</guid><description>Hi there! 👋
I&amp;rsquo;m Benedict, a Software Engineer. This site is dedicated to my personal blog for engineering findings, tips and tricks, and is additionally a portfolio for my projects.
I started this site as a way to learn about static site generators (SSG), and to upgrade the previous version of my website which I wrote entirely using vanilla HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
To learn more about my professional experience, feel free to visit my LinkedIn profile.</description></item></channel></rss>